cvshealth.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy | CVS Health

### Effective Date: August 28, 2018                                            

This Privacy Policy describes how CVS Health Corporation (“CVS,” “we” or “us”) may collect information about you through your interactions with us on CVSHealth.com (the “Website”). By using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or about the way your information is collected and used, please call us toll-free at (888) 607-4287 or email us at [privacy.officer@cvshealth.com](mailto:privacy.officer@cvshealth.com).

We may change this Privacy Policy. The “Effective Date” legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Your use of the Website following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. 

#### Who May Use the Website

We do not knowingly collect personal information online from any person we know to be under the age of 13 and instruct users under 13 not to send us any information to or through the Website.

The Website is designed for users from, and is controlled and operated by us from, the United States. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States or storage of your information in the United States, which may have different data protection rules than those of your country.

#### The Personal Information We Collect

We want you to understand how personal information you provide to us is collected and used. Personal information is any information that we can use to identify, locate, or contact you. We may collect and store your personal information when you provide it to us or to our service providers. Some examples of personal information we collect and when we collect it include:

  * Information about our products or services, such as e-mail alerts, newsletters, and other notifications, when you indicate that you are interested in receiving such information

  * General location information from your browser or device, which we use for internal purposes only

  * Your interactions with our websites or mobile sites

  * When you participate in sweepstakes, surveys or contests that we offer or administer

If you submit any personal information relating to other people in connection with the Website, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Please note that we do not collect patient information through the Website.  

#### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We use your personal information to respond to your requests, such as to send you email alerts, send you newsletters, and to provide you with related customer service. We may also use your information to send marketing communications and administrative information to you.

We may use personal information to personalize your experience interacting with us on the Website, including by presenting products and offers tailored to you, and for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing our Website and new products and services, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and operating and expanding our business activities.

In the event that CVS or some or all of our business, assets or stock are sold or transferred (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) or used as security, or to the extent we engage in business negotiations with third parties, personal information may be transferred to or shared with third parties as part of any such transaction or negotiation.

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may provide personal information to our affiliated businesses or to our business partners, who may use it to send you marketing and other communications.

We may disclose personal information to our service providers, who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfilment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing, and other services.

If we are requested by law enforcement officials or judicial authorities to provide personal information, we may do so. In matters involving claims of personal or public safety or in litigation where the information is pertinent (including to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain), we may use or disclose personal information, including without court process. We may also use or disclose personal information to enforce our terms and conditions, to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates, or to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property and/or that of our affiliates, you, or others.

We may use and disclose personal information to investigate security breaches or otherwise cooperate with authorities pursuant to a legal matter.

We may use and disclose information that does not personally identify you (including the information described under “Cookies and Other Technologies,” below) for any purpose, except to the extent limited by applicable law. If we are required to treat such information as personal information under applicable law, then we may use it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose personal information.

We may combine information that does not personally identify you with personal information. If we do, we will treat the combined information as personal information as long as it is combined.

#### Social Media

We may use and disclose your personal information to facilitate social media sharing functionality that you initiate. If you choose to connect your social media account (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest) with the Website or otherwise engage in social sharing on the Website, your personal information may be shared with your friends, contacts or others associated with your social media account, with other Website users, and with your social media account provider. By connecting the Website and your social media account or contacting us via social media, you authorize us to share information with your social media account provider, and you understand that the use of the information we share will be governed by the social media site’s privacy policy.

For example, if you utilize a social media feature such as the Facebook “Like” button, Google Plus, Pinterest or a Twitter widget, these features may collect information about your IP address and which page you're visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie or employ other tracking technologies. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

We may display targeted ads to you through social media platforms. These ads are sent to groups of people who share traits, such as where they live or have expressed an interest. We do not share any of your personally identifiable information with social media platforms. See the policies of each social media platform for additional information about these types of ads, including how to manage your display settings for these ads.

#### Links

The Website may contain links to, or otherwise make available, third-party websites, services, or other resources not operated by us or on our behalf (“Third Party Services”). These links are provided as a convenience only and do not constitute an affiliation with, endorsement or sponsorship of the Third Party Services. Any information you provide to such third parties is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and we are not responsible for the privacy or security of the information you provide to them or their handling of your information. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any third party to whom you provide personal information online.

In addition, we are not responsible for the information collection, use, disclosure, or security policies and practices of other organizations, such as Apple, Google, Microsoft, RIM, or any other app developer, app provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider, or device manufacturer.

#### Security

We seek to use reasonable physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to protect personal information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately contact us in accordance with the “Contact Information” section below.

#### Cookies and Other Technologies

Like many other websites and online services, we collect information about the Website’s traffic and usage patterns through the use of cookies, web server logs, web beacons and other, similar technologies. We use this information for various purposes, such as to ensure that the Website functions properly, to facilitate navigation, to personalize your experience, to understand use of the Website, to diagnose problems, to measure the success of our marketing campaigns and target advertisements, and to otherwise administer the Website.

Cookies are small computer files we transfer to your computer’s hard drive. These small text files help us personalize content on our pages. Your browser software can be set to reject or accept cookies. Instructions for resetting the browser are available in the Help section of most browsers.

Our use of cookies also allows us to collect and receive certain information about a website user, such as the type of web browser used by our customer. Reviewing our web server logs and our customers’ use of our site helps us to, among other purposes, statistically monitor how many people are using our site and for what purpose.

Pixel tags are a type of technology placed on a website or within the body of an email for the purpose of tracking certain activity, such as views of a website or when an email is open. Pixel tags are often used in combination with cookies.

Your IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider. An IP address may be identified and logged automatically in our web server log files whenever a user accesses the Website, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels of the Website, helping diagnose server problems, and administering the Website.

We may use Adobe Flash Local Stored Objects (“LSOs”) and other technologies to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of the Website. If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the Website Storage Settings Panel. You can also control Flash LSOs by going to the Global Storage Settings Panel and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred to “information” on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time). Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications.

#### Tracking/Third-Party Advertisers

We may use or partner third-party advertising companies, including social media companies like Facebook, as well as third-party advertising companies to provide measurements services and display targeted advertisements regarding goods and services that may be of interest to you when you access and use the Website; these targeted advertisements are based on information relating to your access to and use of the Website and of other online services. To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser, including through the use of pixel tags, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from the Website and elsewhere on the internet. We may use analytics providers that use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and other, similar technologies to collect or receive information about your use of the Website and your use of other websites or online services.

You may opt out of the collection and use of information for advertisement targeting, at any time. To acquire further information and exercise your right to opt out, you may defer to consumer choice tools created under self-regulation programs, such as <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and <http://www.aboutads.info/>. Note: Even if you opt out of targeted advertisements, you may still see or receive other types of online advertising based on factors such as general location derived from your IP address, your browser type, and your search terms.

Lastly, you may manage cookies in your web browser.  Your browser software can be set to reject or accept cookies.  Instructions for resetting the browser are available in the Help section of most browsers.

We do not respond to browser do-not-track signals.

#### Fraudulent Sites, Spam & Phishing

Please be aware that there may be fraudulent websites that illegally use CVS logos, and other aspects of the CVS brand. CVS is in no way associated with any fraudulent websites. These sites may circulate their presence on the internet via spam email, or through fraudulent phishing practices.

These sites have not been authorized by CVS to use our name and we work aggressively to identify their source and have them shut down. If you are in receipt of this type of spam email, to help protect your privacy you should avoid replying to it or forwarding it to other people.

In addition to our official websites, CVS works with a number of third parties that host websites and micro-sites that provide information and services to our customers. If you are concerned that a website or an email may be fraudulent, please contact us by phone at (888) 607-4287 or email [privacy.officer@cvshealth.com](mailto:privacy.officer@cvshealth.com) with your concerns.

#### Your Choices and Access

You can take yourself off our email list for promotional offers at any time by following the instructions contained in such emails. If you opt out of receiving promotional emails from us, we may still send you important administrative messages, from which you cannot opt out.

You can request the removal or modification of the personal information you have provided to us by sending an email to [privacy.officer@cvshealth.com](mailto:privacy.officer@cvshealth.com). For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the personal information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity and obtain information on the context in which you provided your personal information before implementing your request. We will try to accommodate your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion. There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are our customer and a California resident, you may request that we provide you with certain information about the entities with which we have shared our customers’ personal information for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To do so, please write to us at [privacy.officer@cvshealth.com](mailto:privacy.officer@cvshealth.com).

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns about this statement, or about the way your information is collected and used, please email us at [privacy.officer@cvshealth.com](mailto:privacy.officer@cvshealth.com).

If you have any questions about the content of this Privacy Policy, please contact the CVS Health Corporation Privacy Office at the following address:

CVS Health Corporation  
One CVS Drive  
Woonsocket, R.I. 02895  
(888) 607-4287
